啊 我好像又回到我妈的子宫里了
Ah, it's like I'm back in my mother's womb.
只是这里有食物
Only, there's food here.
电子烟这玩意儿真是蠢透了
Ugh, those e-cigs are so stupid.
抽真烟能要你的命
I mean, smoking real cigarettes kills you,
但是抽假烟让我想要了你的命
but smoking fake ones makes me want to kill you.
他们抽的不是烟 是电子烟
They're not smoking. They're vaping.
呃喔 他还把烟递给了她
Uh-oh. He just passed it to her.
人家都在以电子烟之名约会了
Someone's getting date vaped.
我才刚搞清楚新手机咋用
I just figured out the new phones.
现在我还得搞清楚怎么抽烟?
Now I've got to figure out how to smoke?
要是我想把一切都重新学起
If I wanted to learn everything all over again,
我早就中风了
I would have had a stroke.
不好意思 各位 你们这种举动是不允许的
Hey guys, sorry, but you're not allowed to do that in here.
我指的不是你们的装扮
And I'm not talking about your outfits.
我等等给你们找钱的时候再吐槽那个
I'll get to those when I bring the check.
放松点 这不是香烟
Relax, it's not a cigarette.
它有电池的
It has a battery.
是啊 我的震动棒也有电池 但是...
Yeah, so does my vibrator, but...
那个在这里也不能用
can't use that in here either.
但我对那规定也不赞同
I didn't approve that rule.
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组  http://hdscg.com/ ==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 。沫
时间轴: 奥利奥
翻译: Astral  波特妹子  落寞卷菜  morning
校对: 桃茜茜
我觉得咱们订购了太多的纸杯蛋糕裇衫了
Well, I think we ordered too many of our cupcake tees.
这儿没穿过的衣服
There are more unworn shirts here
比马修·麦康纳衣橱里的还多了
than in Matthew MacConaughey's closet.
嘿 姐妹们
Hey, girls.
你们看看我
Look at me.
我穿上了我的周日胸罩 因为我刚从教堂回来
I got my Sunday bra on 'cause I just came from church.
是我经常去的教堂吗?
Was it my church?
后荡妇时代教堂吗?
The Church of Latter-Day Sluts?
Oleg和我在找一个地方作为结婚礼堂
Oleg and I are looking for one to get married in.
而且那个地方一定要有轮椅坡道
And it's got to have a wheelchair ramp
因为我很多堂表亲一出来就没腿骨的
'cause I've got a lot of cousins who were born without leg bones.
我真为你感到高兴 Sophie
I'm so excited for you, Sophie.
你理应是全天下最幸福的女人
You deserve all the happiness in the world.
我也应当如此 但显然我没这种福分了
I mean, so do I, but that's obviously not happening.
你自怜自艾结束了吗?
Are you done with your pity-party?
我要和Max说几句话
'Cause I got to speak to Max.
Max啊 你愿意做我的首席伴娘吗?
Max, do you want to be my maid of honor?
我宁愿被一只兔子活吞了
I would rather be eaten alive by a rabbit.
因为这也要好长时间 但不会让我尴尬
Which would take a long time and be a lot less embarrassing.
Sophie啊 你不是真心想让我
And Sophie, you don't really want me
做你的首席伴娘的
to be your maid of honor.
是啊 我不想
That's right. I don't.
那我们还在讲这件事干什么?
So why are we even talking about it?
Sophie 我很荣幸能受到你的邀请
Sophie, as honored as I am that you asked,
但这事儿真的不适合我啊 你懂吗?
it's just not really my thing, you know, man?
这事儿真的不适合你?
Is this really not your thing?
这事儿就没有谁适合啊
It's nobody's thing.
因为要你做 你就去做啊
You just do it 'cause you're supposed to,
就像刷牙和洗屁眼一样
like bleaching your teeth or your anus.
幸好你没考虑我
Thank God I'm off the list,
因为伴娘水疗日那天一定会难熬极了
'cause that bridesmaid spa day is gonna be rough.
对不起 我当过首席伴娘
Look, I'm sorry, it's just, I was a maid of honor
当时是五年级 我妈妈嫁给了一个邪教教主
in fifth grade when my mom married her cult leader.
一个礼拜之后我和他结婚
And then she was my maid of honor
我妈又是我的首席伴娘
when I married him a week later.
所以我有点不太想当首席伴娘了
So I'm kind of maid-of-honored out.
也许我去找个姐妹会里的旧识
Maybe I'll get one of my old sorority sisters
来当我的伴娘吧
to be my bridesmaid.
我要回家去看看
I'm gonna go home and find out
谁还能瘦得可以坐进商务飞机
which one is still thin enough to fly commercial.
好吧 我们要把这些衣服放在哪里?
All right, where are we gonna store all these shirts?
这里空间已经不够了
It's already too crowded in here
挤满了纸杯蛋糕 羞辱 和失败
with all the cupcakes, shame, and failure.
在我们自家的纸杯蛋糕窗口可以卖掉一些
We'll sell some of these at the cupcake window,
这里的20件已经被卖给了
20 of these are already going
曼哈顿的一家高档的精品时装店
to that fancy boutique in Manhattan,
剩下的么 我们也许会走运
and the rest, maybe we'll get lucky
找到一个同性恋小联盟队
and find a gay little league team.
哦 我知道了!
Oh, I know!
我们去喝醉吧
Let's get drunk.
你什么事情都是这个解决方案
That's your solution to everything.
我说真的
Seriously.
我们得拿一些去那个新开的酒吧
We need to just take some to that new bar
那里的白痴花20美元买一杯酒
where idiots pay $20 for a drink.
一群愚蠢的醉汉 那就是我们的目标人群
Drunk and stupid, that's our target audience.
这特殊技能我在自己的简历里也有写到
And also, the special skills I've listed on my resume.
所以你是说我们已经卑微到这种程度了
So you're saying we're gonna stoop so low
要拿着行李袋去一个酒吧里卖衣服?
as to sell T-shirts out of a duffle bag in a bar?
是的 我们已经堕落了
Yeah, we're there.
你觉得这工作有多少工资?
How much do you think this pays?
我干得了这活啊
'Cause I can do that.
是啊 你干的了
Yes, you can.
你只有一个梯子和一对大胸就行
All you need is a stepladder and boobs.
这地方感觉像是星际迷航:下一代主题酒吧
Feel like the Star Trek: Next Generation bar.
把眼皮给剥了 扮成乌比·戈德堡 再戴个疯帽子
Keep your eyes peeled for Whoopi Goldberg in a crazy hat.
我也无法相信我拿着一个行李袋
I can't believe I'm selling T-shirts out of a duffle bag
在未来卖衣服
in the future, too.
是啊 我完全支持把公事和享乐混在一起
Yeah. I fully support mixing business and pleasure.
我最棒的一次性体验是和老板在帕纳拉面包那次
Best sex I ever had was with my boss at a Panera Bread.
我记得你说过最棒的一次
I thought you said the best sex you ever had
是和一个六个手指的哥们
was with a dude with six fingers.
是同一个人啦
Same guy.
天啊 他做三明治像是疯了一样快
Man, could he make a sandwich crazy fast.
嗨 你想为你的女朋友买一件很酷的T恤吗?
Hi. Want to buy a cool tee for your girlfriend?
我问问我女朋友想不想要T恤
Let me see if my girlfriend wants a tee.
你想要T恤吗 亲爱的?
You want a tee, honey?
嘿! 嘿!
Hey! Hey!
别走那么快啊
Not so fast.
它后面可写着"装满了奶油"呢
They say "cream filled" on the back.
呃 兄弟们? 有感觉吗?
Huh, boys? Anything?
哇 未来的同性恋可一点都不好玩
Wow, gays aren't fun in the future.
嘿
Hey.
耶稣从未来归来
Jesus comes back in the future.
这包里有什么?
So what's in the bag?
我从来没在酒吧见过一个带着行李袋的女孩
I've never met a girl at a bar with actual baggage.
真有趣 因为你是想说我情绪丰富
That's funny because you mean like emotional.
你真的很漂亮
You're really beautiful.
嗯 你在圣经里可没那么帅
Mmm. You weren't nearly this hot in the book.
可否让我请你们喝酒?
So can I get you ladies a drink?
当然可以 你可以直接把这杯水变成酒
Sure, you could just change this water into wine.
你能不能为我 就这样 甩一次秀发?
Can you, like, do this for me, just, like, once?
酒算我的
Drinks on me.
它们艳福不浅啊
Oh, lucky them.
除了流浪汉之外 我已好久没听过别人
I haven't heard I'm beautiful from a non-homeless person
夸我漂亮了
in months.
从他的发型来看 也难确定身份啊
Well, with that hair, the jury's still out.
嘿 我能吻你吗?
Hey, can I kiss you?
我想轻吻一下无妨...
I suppose a peck wouldn't...
神马情况?
Say what?
- 我叫James  - 我湿了
- I'm James.  - I'm wet.
因为我胳膊蹭到吧台上的水了
Because my arm was sitting in water on the bar.
太热辣了 Max
That was so hot, Max.
他对我有种野兽般的狂野吸引力
I have, like, this animal attraction to him.
什么野兽? 饥渴的书呆子?
What animal? The Horny Nerd?
听着 我要走了 你留下来浪吧
Look, I'll leave. You stay and do your thing.
- 但我们是一起来嗨的啊 - 是啊 你们俩挺嗨
- But we came together.  - Yeah, I know you guys did.
他一亲你的时候你就嗨了
It happened, like, the second he kissed you.
这不是我风格 我才刚认识他
I don't do this. I just met him.
听着 Caroline
Look, Caroline.
我没有读过圣经
I haven't read the Bible.
但是我知道当耶稣归来之时
But I know that when Jesus returns,
你必须跟着他回到他的住所
you must follow him back to his apartment.
别拘束...
Let go...
让主耶稣...
let God...
带你走完全程
get to third base.
Max Caroline呢?
Max, where's Caroline?
我一整天没见到她了
I haven't seen her all day.
但我猜她在天堂呢
But I'm guessing she's in heaven.
我来了 我来了
I'm here, I'm here.
不是 她在地狱了
Nope, she's in hell.
彻夜不归 派对荡妹
Walk of shame, party of one.
妞
Girl.
小妞儿!
Gir-irl!
把所有情况都告诉我
Tell me everything that happened.
事无巨细
Leave out no details.
太疯狂了 太火热了
It was insane. I mean, like, so hot.
热得像加勒比海 或像我们上次洗澡那样
Like the Caribbean or our shower that one time.
你们欢呼什么呢?
What are you two celebrating?
我知道肯定不是工作出色
I know it isn't a job well done.
我们在庆祝新的星球大战:第七部
We are celebrating the release
预告片在网上上映了
of the new Star Wars: Episode VII trailer online.
真的吗?
Seriously?
Max 我们什么都做了
Max, we did everything.
我们...
We...
Oleg 能给我们点隐私吗?
Oleg, can you give us some privacy?
怎么?
What?
我不能出现在女厕
I can't be in the ladies' room.
也不能在厨房呆着了
I can't be in the kitchen.
所以你们...
So did you...
没有
No.
好吧 那你们...
Well, did you...
没有!
No!
那你们起码...
Well, did you at least...
天 当然没有!
Oh, God, no!
那你们到底干嘛了?
Well, what did you do?
一起浇花?
Water a plant together?
我们做爱了
We had sex.
昨晚和今天
Last night and today.
这对我来说是件大事
That's a big thing for me.
没错 确实大事
And, yes, it was.
嗯 在酒吧时就很明显
Yes. That was obvious in the bar.
紧身牛仔裤让下体一览无余
Skinny jeans are just boner X-rays.
哦 不 哦 不
Oh, no. Oh, no.
怎么 沙拉里又有老鼠了?
What, rat in the slaw again?
我的戒指
My rings.
我落在他家了
I left them at his place.
我得拿回来
I have to get them back.
它们是我的半副身家了
They're half my belongings.
那就发个短信说 "嘿 我戒指忘拿了
So just text him and say, "Yo, I left my rings,
小弟弟不错" 选个满分的表情 发送
nice wiener" "100" emoji, send.
Max 我不能先给男方发短信
Max, I can't text a guy first.
买润滑油都要团购已经够糟糕了
It's bad enough I have a Groupon for intimacy oil.
最坏的情况 也就是你再也吃不到带"骨"大牛排了
Look, worst-case scenario, the McRib is gone for good.
第二坏的情况就是我们总可以采取
Second worst-case scenario, we can always implement
两周法则嘛
the two-week rule.
两周法则?
The two-week rule?
慢着 就是两周内要吃完泰式炒面
Wait, isn't that how long you have to eat Pad Thai
否则会变质吗?
before it becomes bad Thai?
不是 你真的该读读我的书
No, you really have to read my book.
指的是如果他两周内不发短信
It means if he doesn't text for two weeks,
你就可以闯进他家取回你的东西
you can break in and get your stuff.
白读那么多好学校 你啥也没学到
All that fancy school and you didn't learn nothing.
两周了屁都没有
Two weeks and nothing.
我真以为他会发短信的
I really thought he'd text.
我还以为"长大成人2"会得奥斯卡奖
I also thought Grown Ups 2 should have won the Oscar.
仍然屡猜不中
Still got it.
麻利点
Come on.
等下 在我把剩下的自尊也丢完之前...
Wait, before I lose the rest of my self-esteem...
跟你骑着的那面墙说去
Tell that to the wall you're currently straddling.
让我再查下手机看看他有没有...
Let me just check my phone one more time to see if he...
没有
Nope.
自尊心彻底没了
Self-esteem gone.
我不敢跳
I'm afraid to jump.
跳啊 小贱人 给我跳!
Jump, whore, jump!
听起来像我妈教我游泳似的
I sound like my mom teaching me how to swim.
我做到了 我做到了
I did it. I did it.
墙才两英尺高
That was, like, two feet.
我擤的鼻涕都比这长
I've snorted lines longer.
哎呀呀
All right.
又是普通的一天
Just another Tuesday.
悄悄来到耶稣的后院偷戒指
Going all Bling Ring in Jesus' backyard.
这里 那是他卧室的窗户
There. That's his bedroom window.
我很了解 因为我叫得太大声我们得关窗
I know 'cause we had to close it, since I'm kind of loud.
你在滚床单时都是啥样啊?
Oh, what are you like during sex?
他要是在家怎么办?
What do I do if he's home?
你是想我手起刀落砍了他
Do you want me to kill him fast,
还是慢慢折磨他?
or do you want him to suffer?
折磨的意思是 你想让我抓着他
And by that, I mean, do you want me to hold him
然后你来问他为什么不打电话吗?
while you ask him why he didn't call?
他不在家
He's not home.
看他的更新的状态 他在墨西哥餐厅
According to this Instagram, he's at Chipotle
和一个肩膀上有只鹦鹉的人在聊天
talking to a guy with a parrot on his shoulder.
他忙得没时间发短信给我
He had no time to pop off a text to me.
噢 我要被窗户卡住了 胸都过不去
Oh, it's stuck and I can't fit my boobs through there.
要知道荷兰隧道才刚刚够我的胸挤进去
I can barely fit them through the Holland Tunnel.
好吧 我进去
Fine. I'm going in.
终于 飞机场还是有点用处的
Finally, having no boobs pays off.
把我的腿抬起来
Lift my legs up.
好吧 你一开始来这地方的
Okay, but your legs in the air
契机也是为了要张开双腿
kind of got you here to begin with.
- 呃噢  - 噢什么?
- Uh-oh.  - What oh?
我不记得他的羽绒被有花
I don't remember him having a floral duvet.
旁边还有一个厕所
Or a bedside toilet.
还有一只狗 快把我弄出来!
Or a dog. Pull me out! Pull me out!
你真得好好读读我的书
You've got to read my book.
我有一整章写的都是如何弄出来
I have a whole chapter on pulling out.
不 不 不! 噢 别舔我了
No, no, no, no, no! Oh, stop licking me.
Buster? 怎么了
Buster? Buster?
有人来了
Someone's coming.
有人来了 还被舔了?
Someone's coming or getting licked?
或许这正是你要找的地方啊
Maybe you are in the right apartment.
从我的房间里滚出去! 滚出去!
Get out of my house! Get out of my house!
不 不 你误会了
No, no. This is a big mistake.
Ben 叫警察!
Ben, call the cops!
这儿有个吸毒者!
We got another crack addict here!
我们这里没有毒品!
We don't have crack here!
我们没有毒品! 告诉你的朋友!
We don't have crack here! And tell your friends!
如果这些指纹和07年闯入阿贝餐厅嫌疑犯的指纹相吻合
If these match the prints found at an Arby's break-in in '07,
那纯粹是巧合
it's purely coincidental.
真不敢相信我会发生这种事
I can't believe this is happening to me.
我完蛋了
My life is over.
看镜头
Look at the camera.
我真是没脸见人了
I'm so humiliated.
转过身
And turn to the side.
女士 这不是在拍"时尚:监狱诱惑"
Ma'am, this isn't "Vogue: Behind Bars."
对不起 警官 她还是个处女
Sorry, Officer, she's a virgin.
我曾在普罗维登斯的青少年教养院
Me, myself, spent some time in the juvie system
呆过一段时间
up in Providence.
你认识一个叫做雪莉的家庭法院法官吗?
You know a family court judge named Shelly?
没有 过去
No. Go.
噢! 警官 等一下
Oh! Officer, hold.
谢谢 但是全身检查的时候离我远一点
Thanks, but stay away during the full-body cavity search.
开始吧
Proceed.
要你命令我?
You think?
所以你们两个闯进老婆婆的家里
So you girls broke into an old lady's house,
爬进窗户 却什么都没偷
got halfway through the window, and stole absolutely nothing.
真高兴是我来保护这座城市啊
Glad I am protecting the city from you.
ISIS组织算得了啥
I mean, ISIS who, right?
好了 我们走吧
All right. Let's go.
如果他给我发短信 就不会发生这些事
If he had just texted me, none of this would be happening.
我就不会进监狱 而是呆在家
I wouldn't be in prison, I'd be home.
我的另一个监狱
My other prison.
噢 等下 如果谁给你发短信?
Uh, wait, if who had texted you?
谢谢你的关心
Thanks for asking.
这个家伙把我睡了之后
This guy I slept with didn't text me
就两个星期都没给我发短信 我还把戒指
for two weeks after we had sex, and I left my rings
落在他家 所以我...
at his place, so I...
你这是遵循两周法则?
You did the two-week rule?
是的
Yeah.
但是她找错了地方 你懂的
But she got the wrong apartment because, knowing her,
她在嘿咻的时候全程是闭眼的
her eyes were closed the whole time.
哎 你怎么不早说呢?
Well, why didn't you say so?
这里有一个两周法则的傻瓜!
We got a two-week rule over here!
呆在这里别动
Stay right over here.
一会我们就能放你们走
We'll get you out soon.
我把我的警棍丢在了警长家里
I left my billy club at the Captain's house.
他还有三天时间
He's got three more days.
看见了吗? 看见了吗?
See? See?
没事的
It's gonna be fine.
我们只需要悠闲地等一个小时
We'll just chill here for an hour.
这里就是警局版的亮视点眼镜店
It's like an edgier Lens Crafters.
我该怎么跟我爸爸说呢?
What am I gonna tell my father?
从监狱打电话给监狱?
A prisoned prison call?
我不能呆在这
I can't be here.
我不能呆在这!
I can't be here!
不! 不! 快回来! 我们没事的!
No! No! Come back! We were good!
愚蠢的行动
Dumb move.
比我和队长还愚蠢
Dumber than me and the Captain.
我看 我们的眼镜一个小时是配不好了
Let me guess, our glasses won't be ready in an hour.
简直难以置信 你把我们关到了监狱里
I can't believe you got us arrested in jail.
我们要去哪儿?
Where are we going?
生活已经无处可去
I mean, besides nowhere in life.
这会儿已不能让你们俩免费出狱了
You girls lost your get-out-of-jail-free card.
得有人保释你们才行
You're gonna have to get someone to bail you out.
你们去拘留室待着吧
You're going in the holding cell.
嘿! 小鲜肉来了!
Yo! Fresh meat!
抱歉 我也得维护自己的威望
Sorry, I have a reputation to uphold.
Max 我太害怕了
Max, I'm scared.
交给我
I got this.
嘿! 这婊子已经是我的了!
Yo! She's already my bitch!
谁也别想动她 不好意思了
So she can't be anyone else's. Sorry.
抓着我的皮带
Hold my belt.
- 什么?  - 照我说的做!
- What?  - Do it!
有事吗 有事吗?
'Sup, 'sup?
酷 酷
Cool, cool.
五十个人 一个厕所?
50 women, 1 toilet?
这就像是"视野乐团"的后台啊
It's like backstage at The View.
Max 我受不了了
Max, I can't handle this.
我受不了了
I can't handle this.
我甚至都不忍心看绿里奇迹了
I couldn't even watch The Green Mile.
放轻松 我们只不过是在玩监狱游戏
Relax. This is play-jail.
这可不像是我们平常的游戏
It's not like we're doing real time.
把你玩游戏时的表情摆出来就行了
Just put on your game face.
我哪有玩游戏时的表情
I don't have a game face.
除非是 "我不干了 我的生活完蛋了" 这种游戏
Unless the game is "I Give Up, My Life Is Over,"
我现在就是那种表情
then this will do.
那么 做点什么 不然那个正向我们走来
Well, do something, because that's about to get wiped off
满身纹身的壮女人
your face by the bruiser covered in tattoos
就要撕开你的脸了
making her way to us right now.
嘿!
Hey!
你们是报名参加才艺秀的吗?
You guys signing up for the talent show?
再说一遍?
Excuse me?
我们中有些人已经在这儿好几天了
Yeah. Some of us have been in here for days,
都怪监狱的人太多了
due to prison overcrowding.
所以守卫允许我们搞表演
So the guards let us put on a show.
只要别死人就行
As long as nobody dies.
哇 监狱已经变了
Wow, prison has changed.
我能想象在诺曼•洛克威尔笔下的监狱了
Maybe I have a Norman Rockwell idea of prison,
不过要是在排队打饭时往告密者
but, uh, what happened to shanking a snitch
插上一刀要怎么弄?
in the food line?
哦 才艺秀 这一点也不可怕
Oh, a talent show, that's not scary at all.
告诉你 我在游艇俱乐部才艺比赛
You know, I won my yacht club talent show
10到13岁的小组里 连续赢了三年
three years in a row, in the 10 to 13 division.
这太疯狂了!
That's crazy!
我正看着10至13岁的侠盗车手呢
I'm looking at 10 to 13 for grand theft auto.
我真没礼貌
Where are my manners?
我是Tanaya
I'm Tanaya.
我是Max 这是Caroline
I'm Max. This is Caroline.
但你可以用我们组合的名字叫我们
But you can call us by our gang names,
"白色闪电"和"断刀客"
White Lightning and The Blade.
Sophie 我需要你来保释我和Caroline出狱
Sophie, I need you to bail me and Caroline out jail.
我们因破门入室罪被抓了
We got charged with breaking and entering,
Caroline也让一个家伙入了她的蓬门
which is also what Caroline let a guy do to her,
所以我们才进了这里
and that's why we're here.
天啊 Max
Oh, jeez, Max.
你这来电真让我为难
I mean, that's a tough call.
我不知道自己能不能行啊
I mean, I don't know if I can.
但这事儿我真的干不来啊
Yeah, it's really not my thing.
你懂的 哥们儿?
You know, man?
我明白 是我活该
I get it. I deserved that.
我拒绝了你 所以你也拒绝我
I said no to you, so you're saying no to me.
正如俗话说的"以胸还大胸"
Like the old saying, "Tit for bigger tat."
是啊 嗯
Yeah. Hmm.
好吧 这样吧
All right, let's see.
我会保释我的伴娘出狱
Uh, I would bail my maid of honor out of jail.
好 好
Fine. Fine.
我会当你的伴娘
I'll be your maid of honor.
我会给你买鸡鸡形的吸管 还有
I'll buy you penis straws, and those glasses
鼻子上是个鸡鸡的眼镜
where the nose is a penis.
好! 还要鸡鸡形的意大利面?
Yeah! And the penis-shaped pasta?
我全都照办
I'll do it all.
我不怕坐牢 但是Caroline完全接受不了
I can handle the slammer, but Caroline doesn't stand a chance.
我看见一个女的在盯着她
I saw a woman looking at her
就像她是个卡通猪排一样
like she was a cartoon pork chop.
好了 我们一会儿见
Okay. Well, I'll see you soon.
小心背后
And watch your back.
噢 不对哦
Oh, you know what?
这是女子监狱 所以小心你的前面
It's a ladies' prison, so watch your front.
这是你那张牌吗?
Is this your card?
不是
No.
是!
Yes!
是 这就是我那张牌
Yes, that's my card.
太棒了
Amazing.
好了 我错过什么了?
Okay. What'd I miss?
魔术表演和即兴戏剧
The magic show and the improv troupe.
他们让观众点评一下
They asked the audience for a word.
我说的是 "救命啊"
I said, "Help."
等Sophie的火鸡出炉了
Sophie's coming down with bail money,
她就会带着保释金过来
as soon as her turkey is out of the oven.
四小时 或四个半小时 取决于馅料的多少
So 4, 4 1/2 hours, depending on the stuffing.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
等等 保释我们两个人 对吗?
Wait. Bail for both of us, right?
她最开始不是这么说的
That wasn't her original offer.
但经过一番协商后 我们成功拿下了
But after some negotiating, we got there.
你答应她的条件是...
What did you have to do to...
Max 你不会是答应...
Max, you didn't agree to...
对
Yup.
想象下我穿着低胸露点装的样子
Picture me in something low-cut and peach.
淫荡的样子
A slutty peach.
你为了我这样做的吗?
You'd do that for me?
我既感动又惊讶
I'm touched and shocked.
我还以为你已经把我忘了 跟门卫做爱去了
I thought you'd have forgotten me, had sex with the door guard,
然后现在已经在去停车场的途中
and been halfway across the parking lot by now.
这个嘛 他对我没兴趣 所以就...
Yeah, well, he wasn't into me, so...
蒙羞之旅 二人成双
Walk of shame, party of two.
姑娘们 我听说你们被关起来了
Girls, I heard you got locked up.
是 我们必须做三十小时的社区服务
Yup. We have to do 30 hours of community service.
Caroline还在才艺秀里赢得了六分钟的
And Caroline won six minutes of privacy on the toilet
私人如厕时间
in the talent show.
其实也不是那么私人
Well, not so private.
我尿尿时还得跟一个穿着工作靴的女人
I had to tinkle while a woman in work boots
四目相对
made heavy eye-contact.
我进过一次监狱 因为我在错误的时间
I went to prison once for being at the wrong place
去了错误的地方
at the wrong time.
也就是说 我去了南部
Meaning, I was down south.
看看是谁从"大房子"监狱回来了
Look who's back from the big house.
对你来说 每个房子都是大房子 Han
Every house is a big house for you, Han.
小心脚下 有前科的人
Watch your step, ex-con,
否则我会以冒充服务生的名义让你回监狱去
or I'll get the to haul you back in for impersonating a waitress.
我不敢相信我会说这话 但我想这个地方了
I can't believe I'm saying this, but I missed this place.
我被困在监狱里 和我的姐妹Tanaya一起的时候...
When I was up in the pen, doing time with my girl, Tanaya...
所以 你也要参演女子监狱了吗?
Well, orange you the new black?
你们俩在女子监狱玩的开心吗?
So did you two have fun in ladies' prison?
跟我说说 是不是像我的那些
And tell me, is it anything like the 17 XXX movies
标着17禁的电影一样?
I have with that title?
好吧 我丢了我的两个最好的戒指
Okay, so I lost two of my best rings.
所以我连11美元都没了
So I'm out $11.
我意识到我比自己想的要坚强
I realized I'm tougher than I thought.
我在监狱里唱歌 有了一夜情
I sang in prison. I had a one-night stand.
我差不多赶上约翰尼·卡什了
I'm practically Johnny Cash.
你是约翰尼·没钱
Well, Johnny No Cash.